http://www.thegospelstation.com/privacy-policy.html

Home
Music
Christmas Channel!
Christmas Playlist
Listen Online
What's Playing Now?
Music
Christmas Channel!
Christmas Playlist
Listen Online
What's Playing Now?
Privacy Policy
KTGS is committed to safeguarding individual and corporate privacy on our website; we operate under a strict set of privacy principles.Information We Collect and Receive KTGS collects and retains information about you and your device when you visit or give us information through the KTGS website.Non-Personally Identifiable Information. When your computer or mobile device contacts our web servers, we collect usage information about how our visitors use and navigate the KTGS website. An anonymous profile is established based on your visit and information such as the frequency and length of your visit, browser type, referrer data identifying the web page visited prior and subsequent to visiting the web site, and your IP address. No personally identifiable information is collected without your voluntarily providing it to us.Personally Identifiable InformationWe collect personal information from you, such as your name, mailing address, phone number, and email address only if you voluntarily provide it to us. Once you voluntarily provide KTGS with personal information through our website, any previous anonymous profile associated with your IP address is updated with your personal information, including email address, and your email becomes the primary identifier for your profile.How We Use Your InformationThe information we collect is used to improve your KTGS experience. Visitors are provided services tailored especially for them, or to inform them about new features or services. Occasionally, KTGS conducts user surveys to better target the music we play.While KTGS uses third party vendors to communicate with you, your information, including your email address, will not be sold, shared or disclosed with any third party outside of the KTGS family unless otherwise noted in a specific consent or other entry, or as necessary to provide communications from KTGS through third party vendors. KTGS employs strict security measures to safeguard online transactions, and personal information is stored in a secured database and always sent via an encrypted channel.Other Information You May WantThe KTGS Privacy Policy was updated effective 03/15/17. Cookies are text files that are placed in your device's browser and are used to help recognize your browser across different web pages, websites, and browsing sessions. Cookies are stored on your device. We may use cookies together with other information to enhance and personalize your experience on our Services (or elsewhere online), including:to authenticate your identity when you use our servicesto remember your preferences and registration informationto measure and research the effectiveness of our services, advertisements, and communications to customize the content and advertisements provided to you through our services.Other Information You May WantThe KTGS Privacy Policy was updated effective 03/15/17.Contact us:If you have questions about our privacy policy, please contact KTGS. You may also send mail to South Central Oklahoma Christian Broadcasting Inc:P.O.BOX 1343 Ada Oklahoma 74821Contact KTGS at (800) 557-8815
Sponsors
Privacy Policy
FREE MOBILE APP
Join Our Mailing List
* Indicates required field
Name *
Email *
Submit
1-800-557-8815 • email@thegospelstation.comP.O. Box 1343 Ada, OK 74821
Home
Music
Christmas Channel!
Christmas Playlist
Listen Online
What's Playing Now?
